A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Paris, RG 6, SG 1 FA395
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Pre-war, 1922-1941; 1; 46 Boxes; 28 cubic feet
  - Pre-war - Correspondence, 01
    - MS Holland - Leiden University, 1934-1941 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      Child Psychiatry - Gorter, E. - 1936-1940 Dermatological Department - Siemens, H. W. - 1939-1940 Institute of Physiology - Rademaker, C. G. J. - 1934-1935 Opthalmological Clinic - Van der Hoeve, L. - 1934-1935 Pharmacological Laboratory - de Jongh, S. E. - 1940-1941
    - MS Holland - Utrecht University, 1928-1940 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      Baudet, E. A. R. T. - Institute for Parastic and Infectious Diseases - 1929-1931 Bielchowsky, Max - (Nervous Diseases) - 1933-1934 Institute of Physiology - 1928-1932, 1940 Psychiatric Clinic - 1939-1940
    - MS Hungary - Budapest University, 1928-1937 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Children's Clinic - Kerpel-Fronius, E. - 1934-1937 de Balogh, E. - II Pathological Anatomical Institute - 1928-1929 Medical Library - 1928-1931
    - MS Hungary, 1927-1935 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      Deutsch, Adam - (Physiology) - 1933-1935 Hungarian Fellowship Council - 1928-1935 Medical Education - 1927-1931
    - MS Hungary - Szeged University - Kiss, Ferencz - (Anatomy and Histology), 1930-1934 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - MS Iceland, 1925-1939 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      Dungal, Niels P. - (Pathology and Bacteriology) - 1925-1934 Einarson, Larus - (Pathology, Brain Research) - 1933-1934 Tomasson, Helgi - (Psychiatry) - 1936-1939
    - MS Ireland, 1925-1933 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      Queens University, Belfast - 1927 Trinity College, Dublin - 1925-1933 University College, Dublin - 1928-1929
    - MS Italy - Developmental Aid, 1925-1933 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      Bologna University - 1925-1933 Milan University - 1926-1931 Naples University - 1925-1930 Turin University - 1926-1933
    - MS Italy - Florence University, 1923-1933 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      Institute of Anatomy - 1933 Institute of General Pathology - 1932-1933 Medical Library - 1923-1933
    - MS Italy - Genoa University - Institute of Pharmacology and Experimental Therapy - (Resident Fellowship Program), 1925-1933 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - MS Italy, 1932-1938 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      Gualtierotti, Torquato - Milan University - Institute of Physilogy - 1939 Jucci, Carlo - Modena University - Institute of Zoology and Comparative Anatomy and Physiology - 1932-1937 Margaria, Rodolfo - (Physiology) - 1933-1938
    - MS Italy, 1925-1940 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      Pavia University - (Physiology, Anatomy) - 1925-1933 Pentimalli, Francesco - (General Pathology) - 1926-1934 Scotti-Fogliani, Luigi - (Biochemistry) - 1931-1940
    - MS Japan - Kitasato, Shibasaburo - (Memorial, Medical Education), 1931 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - MS Yugoslavia, 1924-1930 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      Belgrade University - Medical Faculty - 1924-1928 Zagreb University - (Veterinary Science, Pathology) - 1929-1930
    - MS Lithuania - Siaulis, Benedict - (Pharmacology), 1927 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - MS Norway - Oslo University, 1929-1940 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      Anatomical Institute - 1934-1939 Folling, Asbjorn - Physiological Institute - 1929-1930, 1937 Gjessomg, R. R. - Dikemark Mental Hospital - 1937-1939 Psychiatric Clinic - Langfeldt, Gabriel - 1937-1940 Psychiatric Clinic - Odegaard, Arnulf and Vogt, Ragnar - 1936-1937
    - MS Palestine - Hebrew University, Jerusalem - (General Correspondence), 1934-1938 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - MS Poland, 1922-1936 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      Cracow University - Medical Faculty - 1922-1930 Poznan University - Medical Faculty - 1924-1928 Warsaw University - Neurobiological Institute - Cherobski, George - 1934-1936
    - MS Portugal, 1924-1939 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      Lisbon University - Celestino da Costa, A. P. - Institute of Histology and Embryology - 1933-1939 Lisbon University - Faculty of Medicine - 1924-1936 Lisbon University - Neurological Institute - 1934-1935 Porto University - Medical Faculty - 1928-1936
    - MS Roumania, 1923-1937 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      Bucharest University - Boivin, Andre - (Biochemistry) - 1931-1935 Cluj University - (Fellowships) - 1924 Iassy University - (Fellowships) - 1923 Iassy University - Ionescu-Mihaesti, C. - (General Pathology) - 1928 Iassy University - Popa, Gregor T. - (Anatomy) - 1930-1937
    - MS Roumania, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      "Report on the Present Situation and the Problems of Organization of the Department of Pathological Anatomy, Medical School, University of Bucharest"
    - MS Russia, 1923-1934 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      Kasan University - Medical Literature - 1926-1932 Kharkov Psychoneurological Institute - Medical Literature - 1930-1934 Kupalov, P. S. - Institute of Experimental Medicine, Leningrad - Physiological Laboratory - 1929-1930 Orbeli, L. - Leningrad Military Acdemy - Institute of Physiology - 1928-1933 Pavlov, Ivan P. - (Physiology) - 1923-1925 Tiflis University - Physiological Laboratory - 1933
    - MS Scotland, 1930-1939 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      Aberdeen University - (Practice of Medicine Department) - (Rheumatoid Arthritis Research) - 1934-1935 Dott, Norman M. - (Neurosurgery) - 1936-1938 Edinburgh Royal Infirmary - 1930-1936 Edinburgh University - Department of Physiology - 1934-1935 Henderson, D. K. - (Psychology) - 1935-1939
    - MS Sweden, 1927-1940 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      Ekehorn, Gosta - (Kidney Research) - 1927-1928 Liljestrand, G. - (Pharmacology) - 1934-1935, 1938 Theorell, Hugo - (Medical Chemistry) - 1934-1935 Upsala University - Institute of Pathological Anatomy - 1930 Upsala University - Medical Clinic - 1934-1939 Upsala University - The State Institute for Human Genetics and Race Biology - 1940 Von Euler, Ulf - (Pharmacology) - 1931-1935
    - MS Switzerland - Bern University, 1931-1940 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      Ascher, Leon - Physiological Institute - 1931-1937 Psychiatric Clinic - Georgi, Felix K. - 1934-1938 Psychiatric Clinic - Grunthal, Ernst - 1934-1940
    - MS Switzerland - Geneva University, 1935-1938 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      Anatomical Laboratory - Weber, A. - 1935-1935 Anatomical Laboratory - Szepsenwol, J. - 1936-1937 Institute of the Sciences of Education - Piaget, Jean - 1935-1938
    - MS Switzerland - Zurich University, 1934-1940 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      Institute for Brain Anatomy - 1933-1939 Katzenstein, Rich - Polyclinic for Nervous Diseses - 1935-1939 Physiological Institute - Hess, W. B. - 1934-1940 Physiological Laboratory - Wyss, O. - 1937-1938 Psychiatric Clinic - 1934-1938 Sugical Clinic - 1936-1937
    - MS Syria - American University of Beirut, 1932-1937 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      (Biological Chemistry) - 1934-1937 Department of Medicine (Biological Chemistry) - 1932-1936
    - MS USA - Burks, Barbara - (Psychology), 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - MS Wales - Quatel, Juda H. - (Brain Chemistry), 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - MS General - Miscellaneous Fellowship Expenditure Fund, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - NS Austria - Tierarztliche Hochschule, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - NS Bulgaria - Sofia University - Faculty of Agriculture, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - NS Denmark - Bohr, Nils - (Physics), 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - NS England, 1925-1938 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      Cambridge University - Plymouth Marine Biological Station - Library - Physical and Biological Sciences - 1925-1938 Rothamsted Experiment Station - (Glasshouses) - 1928 University College, London - 1935-1936
    - NS Finland - (Miscellaneous Fellowship Correspondence), 1925-1936 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - NS France - Paris University - (Miscellaneous), 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - NS Germany, 1930-1937 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      Butenandt, A. - (Chemistry) - 1934 Declinations - Feller, Willy - (Mathematics) - 1933-1938 Declinations - Fraenkel-Conrat, H. - (Medical Chemistry) - 1936 Freiburg University - Institute of Physical Chemistry - 1930-1931 Freiburg University - Seeman, H. (Physics) - 1932 Kaiser Wilhelm Institute for Biology - 1931-1937 Weber - (Physical Chemistry) - 1931
    - NS Holland, 1932-1940 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      Amsterdam University - (Biochemical Embryology) - 1938-1940 Amsterdam University - Laboratory of General Pathology - 1934-1937 Leiden University - Observatory - 1934-1939 Leiden University - Pharmacological Laboratory - de Jongh, S. E. - 1936-1938 Leiden University - Zoological Laboratory - Boschma, H. - 1932-1934
    - NS Holland, 1931-1939 (Box 9, Folder 93)
      Utrecht Botanical Laboratory - Heyn, A. N. - 1934-1937 Utrecht University - Comparative Physiology - Comparative Physiology - 1934-1936 Utrecht University - Physical Laboratory - 1938-1939 Waginen College of Agriculture - 1931-1932
    - NS Hungary, 1924-1941 (Box 9, Folder 94)
      Budapest Technical University - 1931-1941 Farkas, L. - (Physical Chemistry) - 1934 Huzella, Theodor - Budapest University - Institute of Anatomy - 1924-1938 Royal Hungarian Joseph Technical University - 1930 Schmid, R. F. - (Spectroscopy) - 1933-1937 Sopron High School for Mining Engineers - (undated) Tihany Biological Station - 1933-1936 Zucker, F. - (Chemistry) - 1936
    - NS Ireland, 1932-1937 (Box 9, Folder 95)
      Flynn, T. Thompson - Queens University, Belfast - (Zoology) - 1932-1936 Gatenby, J. Bronte - (Zoology) - 1935-1937
    - NS Italy, 1933-1938 (Box 9, Folder 96)
      Abetti, Giorgio - (Astrophysics) - 1934 Levi, G. - Turin University - Institute of Human Anatomy - 1935-1937 Montalente, G. - Rome University - Institute of Zoology - 1933-1938 Pasquini, P. - Perugia University - Institute of Zoology - 1933 Rasetti, F. - Rome University - Institute of Physics - 1933
    - NS Yugoslavia, 1934-1941 (Box 9, Folder 97)
      Kenk, Roman - Ljubljana University - Zoological Laboratory - 1935 Szeged University - Institute of Medical Chemistry - 1934-1941
    - NS Roumania - Ephrussi, Boris - (Embryology), 1933-1935 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - NS Latvia - University of Latvia, 1931-1939 (Box 9, Folder 99)
      Institute of Physics - 1932-1935 Laboratory of Inorganic Chemistry - 1931-1936 Zoophysical Laboratory - Albolin, A. L. - 1938-1939
    - NS Norway - Oslo University, 1932-1946 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      Jacobsen, A. P. - Endocronology) - 1937 Institute for Genetics - 1934-1946 Institute of Theoretical Astrophysics - 1932 Tromso Observatory - 1932
    - NS Poland, 1927-1940 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      Chrobak, Luwik - Jagellonian University of Cracow - Mineralogical Institute - 1934-1939 Godlewski, Emil - University of Cracow - Biological and Embryological Institute - 1927-1928 Grodzinski, Z. - (Anatomy) - 1929-1940 Kopec, Stefan - Warsaw University - Biological Laboratory - 1934-1935 Lwow University - Laboratory of Chemistry - Parnas, J. - 1935-1936 Pulawy Institute of Agricultural Research - 1927-1932 Pulawy Institute of Agricultural Research - Barbacki, S. - 1938-1939 Pulawy Institute of Agricultural Research - Kaufman, Laura - 1938-1939 Slizynski, B.M. - (Refugee, Cytology) - 1939 Warsaw University - Physical Institute - 1936
    - NS Poland - Wierzuchowski, M. - (Physiology), 1926-1939 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - NS Portugal - Lisbon Institute of Oncology, 1934-1936 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - NS Roumania, 1931-1937 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      Bujorean, George - Cluj University - Institute of Systematic Botany - 1932-1933 Gavrilescu, N. - Bucharest University - Institute of General Physiology - 1931-1937
    - NS Russia - Stern, Lina - (Physiology), 1928-1935 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - NS Scotland, 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      Aberdeen University - Natural History Department - 1937-1940 Edinburgh University - Barger, G. - (Medical Chemistry) - 1936-1937 Edinburgh University - Beevers, C.A. - (X-Ray Crystallography) - 1939-1940 Edinburgh University - Zoology Department - 1931-1934 Muller, H.J. - Edinburgh University - (Animal Genetics) - 1933-1938
    - NS Spain - National Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - NS Sweden, 1926-1939 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      Karolinska Institute - Chemistry Department - Hammarsten, Einar - 1932-1939 Lund University - Department of Physiological Chemistry - Widmark, Erick M. - 1936-1939 Lund University - Westman, Axel E. - (Gynecology and Obstetrics) - 1936-1938 Lundgardh, Hendrik - Hallands Vadero Ecological Station - 1926-1929
    - NS Sweden - Stockholm University, 1927-1939 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      Botanical Institute - Stalfelt, M.G. - 1929-1932 Von Euler, H. - Biochemical Institute - 1927-1939
    - NS Sweden - Stockholm University - Zoophysiology Department - Runnstrom, J., 1932-1939 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - NS Sweden - Upsala University, 1932-1939 (Box 11, Folder 111)
      Institute of Medical Chemistry - Teorell, Torsten - 1936-1938 Institute of Medical Chemistry - Tiselius, Arne - 1932-1939
    - NS Sweden - Upsala University - Laboratory of Physical Chemistry, 1926-1934, 1935-1940 (Box 11, Folder 112)
      I
    - NS Sweden - Upsala University - Laboratory of Physical Chemistry, 1926-1934, 1935-1940 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - NS Sweden - Upsala University - Medical Faculty, 1934-1939 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - NS Switzerland, 1933-1940 (Box 11, Folder 115)
      Basel University - Gerlach, Walter - Institute of Pathological Anatomy - 1933-1937 Basel University - Verzar, Fritz - Physiological Institute - 1933-1940 Bern University - Botanical Institute - Schopfer, H. - 1936 Bern University - Signer, Rudolf - Chemical Institute - 1936-1939 Bern University - Zoological Institute - 1938-1939
    - NS Switzerland, 1926-1939 (Box 11, Folder 116)
      Geneva University - Laboratory of Organic Chemistry - 1936 Geneva University - Zoological Institute - 1932-1936 Kuhn, Werner - (Physical Chemistry) - 1926-1937 Swiss Alpine Station - 1935-1939 Zurich University - Henri, Victor - (Spectrograph) - 1930 Zurich University - Institute of Plant Pathology - 1939 Zurich University - Vonwiller, Paul - (Anatomy) - 1931
    - NS USA, 1926-1927 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      Committee on Intellectual Cooperation - 1926 Dunn, L. C. - (Animal Genetics) - 1927 Evans, H. M. - (Animal Nutrition) - 1927 Kraus, E. J. - (Botany Survey) - 1926-1927
    - NS General - Miscellaneous Fellowship Actions, 1930-1939 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - IHD Personnel - Balfour, Marshall C., 1939 (Box 12, Folder 119)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Permanently restricted - Confidential material.
    - IHD Personnel - Barlow, Claude H., 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - IHD Personnel - Bates, Marston, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - IHD Personnel - Bruno, Alexander, 1917-1939 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - IHD Personnel - Carter, Joseph C., 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - IHD Personnel - Collins, Ralph K., 1939 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - IHD Personnel - Crowell, F. Elisabeth, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - IHD Personnel - Crowell, F. Elisabeth, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - IHD Personnel - Crowell, F. Elisabeth, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - IHD Personnel - Gordon, Francis B., 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - IHD Personnel - Grant, John B., 1930-1939 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - IHD Personnel - Grant, John B., 1930-1939 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - IHD Personnel - Grant, John B., 1930-1939 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - IHD Personnel - Hackett, Lewis W., January-September 1939 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - IHD Personnel - Hackett, Lewis W., January-September 1939 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - IHD Personnel - Hill, Rolla B., 1939 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - IHD Personnel - Hughes, Thomas P., 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - IHD Personnel - Hydrick, John L., 1939 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - IHD Personnel - Jacobs, Henry R., 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - IHD Personnel - Jacocks, William P., 1935-1939 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - IHD Personnel - Janney, John H., 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - IHD Personnel - Janney, John H., 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - IHD Personnel - Delevey, Marie Madeleine - (Formerly Mrs. W. Leland Mitchell), 1933-1939 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - IHD Personnel - Mahaffy, Alexander, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - IHD Personnel - Mahaffy, Alexander, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - IHD Personnel - Platzer, Mary, 1929-1939 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - IHD Personnel - Platzer, Mary, 1929-1939 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - IHD Personnel - Russel, Paul F., 1926-1939 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - IHD Personnel - Russel, Paul F., 1926-1939 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - IHD Personnel - Russel, Paul F., 1926-1939 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - IHD Personnel - Sawyer, Wilbur A., 1932-1939 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - IHD Personnel - Sawyer, Wilbur A., 1932-1939 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - IHD Personnel - Sawyer, Wilbur A., 1932-1939 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - IHD Personnel - Schwentker, Francis F., 1937-1939 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - IHD Personnel - Schwentker, Francis F., 1937-1939 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - IHD Personnel - Smith, Hugh H., 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - IHD Personnel - Smithburn, Kenneth, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - IHD Personnel - Soper, Fred L., 1933-1939 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - IHD Personnel - Soper, Fred L., 1933-1939 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - IHD Personnel - Soper, Fred L., 1933-1939 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    - IHD Personnel - Stratman-Thomas, Warren R., 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 159)
    - IHD Personnel - Strode, George K., January-July 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - IHD Personnel - Strode, George K., January-July 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - IHD Personnel - Sweet, W. C., 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - IHD Personnel - Taylor, Richard M., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - IHD Personnel - Taylor, Ruth, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - IHD Personnel - Tennant, Mary Elisabeth, 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - IHD Personnel - Theiler, Max, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - IHD Personnel - Thoman, Candace, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - IHD Personnel - Warren, Andrew J., 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - IHD Personnel - Warren, Andrew J., 1934-1939 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - IHD Personnel - Wright, Daniel E., 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 170)
    - IHD Personnel - Wright, Daniel E., 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - IHD Africa, 1937-1939 (Box 17, Folder 172)
      Kauntze, W. H. - (Public Health) - 1937-1939 Pridie, Eric D. - (Travel, Yellow Fever) - 1937-1939 Reid, R. D. - (Travle, Yellow Fever) - 1938-1939 Smith, E. C. - (Pathology) - 1938
    - IHD Africa - Symes, Cecil Bernard - (Entomology), 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    - IHD Africa - Symes, Cecil Bernard - (Entomology) - Report, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 174)
    - IHD Albania - Buzo, Zihni - (Fellowship, Sanitary Engineering), 1932-1939 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - IHD Albania - Tirana Health Service, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - IHD Austria - Quastler, Heinrich - (Malaria Research Laboratory, Tirana, Albania), 1939 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - IHD Austria - Ratschky, Lene - (Nursing), 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - IHD Belgium - Archives de Medecin Sociale et D'Hygiene et Revue de Pathologie et Physiologie de Travail, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - IHD Belgium - Daive, Lucienne - (Nursing), 1935-1939 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - IHD Belgium - Delaet, Maurice - (Travel, Public Health), 1939 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - IHD Belgium - Ecole Edith Cavell-Marie Depage - (Nursing), 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - IHD Belgium - Ecole Edith Cavell-Marie Depage - (Nursing), 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 183)
    - IHD Belgium - Mechelynck, Cecile - (Nursing), 1923-1928 (Box 17, Folder 184)
    - IHD Belgium - Opplinger, Zoe - (Nursing), 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    - IHD Belgium - Public Health, 1926-1939 (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Petrich Malaria Field Study, 1932. 1937-1939 (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Public Health, 1934-1939 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Public Health Nursing, 1922-1937 (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Health Center, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 190)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Institute of Hygiene, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Institute of Hygiene, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Nursing Schools, 1925-1935 (Box 18, Folder 193)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Rural Health Demonstration Service, 1926, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    - IHD Bulgaria - Sofia Rural Health Demonstration Service, 1926, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 195)
    - IHD Canada - Fidler, Nettie - (Nursing), 1939 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - IHD China - Hsu-ai-chu - (Nursing), 1939 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - IHD Cyprus - Demonstration in Control of Soil Pollution, 1936-1938 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - IHD Cyprus - McLaughlan, Alan Heartly Philip - (Fellowship, Sanitary Engineering), 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 199)
    - IHD Cyprus - Malaria Investigations, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 200)
    - IHD Cyprus - Malaria Investigations, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - IHD Cyprus - Public Health, 1930-1939 (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - IHD Cyprus - Public Health Nursing, 1936-1939 (Box 19, Folder 203)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Cakrtova, Maria Makowska - (Fellowship, Vital Statistics), 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 204)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Cancik, Joseph - (Travel, Hygiene), 1924, 1934-1939 (Box 19, Folder 205)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Deposed Scholars - (Public Health), 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 206)
      Gruschka, Dr. - 1937-1938 Woltar, S. - 1939 Kellner, Arnost - 1939 Glesinger, Eugene - 1939 Ressek, Dr. - 1939 Neumann, Kamil - 1939
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Drbohlav, Jaroslav - (Fellow, Public Health), 1921-1939 (Box 19, Folder 207)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Drbohlav, Jaroslav - (Fellow, Public Health), 1921-1939 (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Fierlinger, Otokar - (Fellow, Town Planing), 1924-1925, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 209)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Goldbachova, Zdenka - (Nursing), 1939 (Box 19, Folder 210)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Hanak, theodore - (Public Health), 1939 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Houzvicova, Amalia - (Nursing), 1931-1939 (Box 20, Folder 212)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Humbursky, Hugo - (Fellowship, Epidemiology), 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 213)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Jedlicka-Pulitzerova, Gertrud - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1932-1939 (Box 20, Folder 214)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Klima, Jaroslav - (Fellowship, Public Health), 1931-1939 (Box 20, Folder 215)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Lowi, Walter - (Deposed Scholar, Medicine), 1939 (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Pozdilkiva, Mary - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1926-1939 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Prague School for Nurses in Public Health and Social Medicine, 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 218)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Prague State Institute of Public Health, 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 219)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Singer, Ernst - (Travel, Hygiene), 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 220)
    - IHD Czechoslovakia - Strimpl, Vaclov - (Public Health), 1933-1939 (Box 20, Folder 221)
    - IHD Denmark - Aarhus Health Center, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 222)
    - IHD Denmark - Aarhus Post Graduate School for Nurses, 1936-1939 (Box 21, Folder 223)
    - IHD Denmark - Berkild, Helfrid - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 224)
    - IHD Denmark - Epidemiology, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 225)
    - IHD Denmark - Holm, Johannes - (Travel, Tuberculosis), 1933-1939 (Box 21, Folder 226)
    - IHD Denmark - Jacobsen, Karen Margrethe - (Nursing), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 227)
    - IHD Denmark - Jensen, Kai Adolf - (Travel, Tuberculosis), 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 228)
    - IHD Denmark - Kjolner, Inga Van Hadeln - (Fellowship, Nursing), 1939 (Box 21, Folder 229)
    - IHD Egypt - Central Administration, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 230)
    - IHD Egypt - Control of Soil Pollution and Sanitary Engineering, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 231)
    - IHD Egypt - Control of Soil Pollution and Sanitary Engineering, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 232)